<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>History on Neelan Nair</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/history/</link>
    <description>Recent content in History on Neelan Nair</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2014 15:55:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/history/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hitler : Nemesis (Book Review)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hitler-nemesis-book-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2014 15:55:04 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hitler-nemesis-book-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;by Ian Kershaw&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In an attempt to better understand Hitler’s character and maybe pick up some interesting new stories, I started reading another tome, Hitler - Nemesis (1936-45) by Ian Kershaw.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/hitler-nemesis.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Hitler Nemesis Book Cover&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a very dense book, with long chapters and a lot of citations. Its not light reading and took me a year or so of reading it off and on to complete.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One aspect of the story is Kershaw’s theory that a great majority of the German people were indeed in support for a majority of Hitler’s plans. Like all things in history, this is not something I can agree with wholeheartedly because it is a theory and there are those that don’t think it to be the case. The concept of ‘working towards the führer’ where, though there was no direct command from Hitler for most of the atrocities of the war, the machinery of the government filled out the blanks left by Hitler’s vague comments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great War for Civilization (Book Review)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/great-war-for-civilization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 15:55:04 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/great-war-for-civilization/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;by Robert Fisk&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This book is a tome. It weighs in at 1286 pages and another 50 pages of bibliography and notes. It has taken me the best part of 6 months of reading – in bits and pieces – to get through it. Probably because of the way I read it, but also because of the sheer depth and breadth of what is covered in this book, I don’t have a quick summary. I can only tell you my learnings and lasting images. These aren’t pretty images and this is not a book for the faint hearted.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
