<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Culture on Neelan Nair</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/culture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Culture on Neelan Nair</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/culture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Death of a Bookshop</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/death-of-a-bookshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/death-of-a-bookshop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The signs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Buy 1 book get 3 free!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;70% off on all books&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Empty shelves. Unkempt books. The last remains of a once popular bookshop. The couches and beanbags tossed to a side.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Second hand dealers making away with carton loads of books, emptying the shelves as we browse. The death rattle for what was once a bustling refuge for the lettered class of society.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I had never watched a bookshop close in this fashion before. Imagine the state of Foyles in London if that were to close in this way. It seems to me only a matter of time. Amazon will claim many more lives in the coming years.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reading Magazines While We Still Can</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/reading-magazines-while-we-still-can/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 15:38:42 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/reading-magazines-while-we-still-can/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ah the joy of finding a new magazine with great articles. I have found a new love – long form narrative journalism.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It started on my trip to San Francisco from work last December. The apartment I was staying in had a few hundred New Yorker magazines piled up. On weekday nights I could walk around San Fran and experience the city, but I didn’t want to splurge or get mugged, and was quite happy putting my feet up and reading. So I got stuck into those New Yorker magazines.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
